export const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        key: "business scope",
        prompt: "Can you describe what your business does on a day-to-day basis?",
        test_answer: "I'm a pastry cheif, working in my own workshop. I bake cakes, deserts by pre-order. I produce only classical natural deserts, without vegan or sugarl free options."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        key: "typical customers",
        prompt: "Who are your typical customers or clients? What do they come to you for?",
        test_answer: "Women, ordering wedding cakes or some sweets for their family occasions (birthdays)"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        key: "proudest achievements",
        prompt: "What are some of your proudest achievements with your business so far?",
        test_answer: "I've produced 1500 kilos of cakes during the summer season. I've served a wedding for 150 people"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        key: "future vision",
        prompt: "Where do you envision your business in the next 2-5 years?",
        test_answer: "I want my own cafe with deserts."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        key: "recent challenges",
        prompt: "Are there any particular challenges or roadblocks you've faced recently?",
        test_answer: "Manage my time and delegate - I do everything by myself, and have a couple of girls helping in the kitchen only. Routines consume a lot of my time"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        key: "competitive disadvantage",
        prompt: "Have there been any situations where you felt your business was at a disadvantage compared to competitors?",
        test_answer: "No, I'm the best"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        key: "recurring problems",
        prompt: "Are there any recurring problems or challenges that you face, and how do you currently address them?",
        test_answer: "Routine takes a lot of my time"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        key: "new markets",
        prompt: "Are there any new areas or markets you're considering exploring with your business?",
        test_answer: "I want my own cafe with deserts. Also, I want to run workshops to teach other professionals and amauters, and run a new info product (online guide with recepies)"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        key: "customer needs",
        prompt: "Have customers or clients ever expressed a desire or need that you haven't been able to fulfill yet?",
        test_answer: "Mastic figures for cake - and my value is that I conciously don't want to work with it, producing only natural deserts."
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        key: "industry trends",
        prompt: "Are there any trends in your industry that you're excited about or think might impact your business?",
        test_answer: "Same day delivery in mid market segment, unique custom made cakes for luxury events" 
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        key: "external concerns",
        prompt: "Are there any industry changes or external factors you're concerned about?",
        test_answer: "Economical crysis, people might have less money to pay for deserts. Also, price for supplies will go up."
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        key: "competition perception",
        prompt: "How do you feel about the current competition in your market? Are there any emerging competitors you're keeping an eye on?",
        test_answer: "I'm a leader, they learn from me and copy me. Also, we're friends with the most of them and often reach out for help to each other"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        key: "industry changes",
        prompt: "Are there any regulatory, economic, or technological changes you foresee affecting your business?",
        test_answer: "I need to become 100% complient with regulatory requirements (how to produce consumable goods)"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        key: "assessment methods",
        prompt: "Have you ever tried to assess the strengths and weaknesses of your business formally or informally? If so, how did you go about it?",
        test_answer: "I didn't have time to assess my business before"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        key: "decision uncertainties",
        prompt: "Were there ever moments where you felt uncertain about a business decision and wished you had more insights or data to guide you?",
        test_answer: "No, I just trusted my gut feeling"
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        key: "strategic tools",
        prompt: "What tools or methods do you currently use to make strategic decisions or plan for the future of your business?",
        test_answer: "I just trusted my gut feeling"

    },
    {
        id: 17,
        key: "feedback methods",
        prompt: "How do you generally gather feedback or insights about your business performance?",
        test_answer: "I ask my customer directly. Also, if I have $2500 by the end of the month after taxation, salaries, loans and supplies, it was a good performance"
    }
];